foreign
release
pictures
welcome to such an aggravity Suave
um foreign
okay
we started
so
last night we started a special home
yeah
it was written uh 400 years ago foreign
they go and look for the baby
then they find him and then he has to
grow up
it's about 21 or 25 he can take power
then usually during that time the petrol
mama takes care of today
yeah number one
so the first potential number was very
very beautiful man
foreign
can you bring some more cheers okay
great writer great point
yeah
and a good dancer he was a good dancer
religious stuff
issues as we said yesterday he was a
great pacifist
Pacific
one time as I said last night there was
going to be a Civil War in Tibet is
he heard about it and he went and he
stood between the two armies and he said
if you're going to fight you have to
kill him
and then they stopped the world
he wrote many books about meditation
this book we are studying is about
meditation it's
a meditation called mahamudra
meditations
in the beginning means to what the one
part of the Mind watches the other part
of the line
um
so the this part of the Mind watches
this part of the mind is this part of
the Mind meditating well or not if this
part of the Mind thinks about khazar
then this part of the mind will raise
alarm
you set back to yourself
he will say don't think about you you
think about meditation
so this is very useful
and if you make your mind strong
you can accomplish many things
your mind wants to avoid problems
your mind is a little bit lazy
um
you have to think about lunch
he wants to think about after work
train this part of the mind to watch
that part of them
then when you are supposed to finish
some work then this part of the mind he
he's the policeman for this part is
person if you learn to watch your own
life
you can succeed at anything
most of us we are just living in San
Ramon a
um
and we just do what the mind says
in this system no system now you learn
to watch your own thoughts
and then uh when when it's not thinking
about the thing you're supposed to think
about this will bring the Mind back
parties
then last night we talked about a
special a special kind of watching the
month
one is for example say uh we have to
finish this job we have to finish this
job in today by three o'clock
part of the mindset I don't know let's
have a cafe
maybe we can finish tomorrow
this one is lazy and this one is trying
to finish the job
and then a third part of your mind is
watching the other two parts of your
life
by watching it you can win the fight
if you don't watch the fight
all right so in this system pencil
roller
systems we learned to watch
that we have to watch
and we talked about it last night
we were talking about aspects
last night we had a big talk about
aspirin
we were trying to decide if Aspen works
when I said
in March
or does their car work
so much or do Stark Investments work
um
we're just going to work work
or does yoga work
we talked about it last night and about
to say yeah so I'll I'll just summarize
what we said yesterday
what is this thing is
in Tibet they always ask questions
it prevents the student from sleeping
because we have to get up at three
o'clock
we worked very hard
and in the class you don't like class
the first boy is the best boy
behind them is this other boys foreign
then the teacher will take the first boy
who pull his hand
then six points
so my teacher he always asks a lot of
questions
thank you
is it a medicine yes yes
it takes away pain cures pain
the reason for medicine is to cure
something
her shoes
am I right
sometimes
then I gave example yesterday about an
airplane
if you go to the airport
you get on the you try to get on the
airplane it was
he said you asked them do you know how
to fly this airplane
if they say sometimes
sometimes it flies very well
what's it mean sometimes
what's the meaning of sometimes
it means sometimes it doesn't fly
foreign
if the airplane flies sometimes if the
airplane falls down sometimes is it a
good airplane
is it a passenger airplane
I mean it's a killing passenger
but can we say it's not a passenger
foreign
if the student gives a bad answer
then the boy comes out of the class he
has a red dot yeah hello
then all the other young monks they are
laughing at him
okay so be careful
if the airplane falls
sometimes and flies sometimes is it a
passenger airplane no excuse me
here's a medicine
it works sometimes and it doesn't work
sometimes
you have to say no
um
we said yesterday there's a thing in
here called the active ingredient
there's something inside the aspirin
which makes the aspirin work yeah
in the television when the new ly makes
it aspirin what do they say
um
this one really works
when you hear somebody say really works
you have to be careful
this investment really works
um
buying this building will really make
you really works making money
this Aspen really works
why do they say really
that's the reason to say really
I'm not just talking philosophy
you make investment you try to make
money right
you make a company
you get a jump
even one day when you wake up one day
you don't know it if you live the whole
day or not you don't know
in Tibet they don't say maybe you will
die today
you will die today
and one day it becomes true
so we don't everything we do we
we don't know we hope
to conference
and what I'm trying to say what I I what
I want to say tonight you don't have to
live like them
it's not necessary to live with uh
uncertainties
maybe you will make money today maybe
you won't make money today but foreign
doesn't matter to me
if there's a way
that we can get Aspen to work
if there's a way to make money without
uncertainty
attitude
if there's a way to
it becomes a way to make sure your
boyfriend was dead
or your husband will treat you with
respect
then then that's enough for me that I
think that's like a religion I don't
know that's enough for myself
so uh
there is a way
and I I don't care I don't want you to
join anything
you don't have to wear special clothes
I just want to show you something and
then you go home and you use it
maybe I'll meet you again maybe not
but next year you should be rich okay
if you understand what I'm teaching
I we called last night
you have money enough you don't have to
think about it is
I I don't uh someone else takes care of
my money I don't know how much there is
said yeah and my relationship
s
and it's not uh
accidentally
I made the course
she created
I have this relationship
so I just want to show you how to do
then you have a nice relationship yeah
and you have oxygen money
and then you can do what you want yeah
okay so I have to
we with we say
inside the Aspen there is no active
ingredient
this is wrong what they put on the
bottle is wrong
there is not an active ingredient in the
in the Australian phenomena
if there was an active ingredient in the
aspirin then when you take it it should
stop you baby all the time
so
that ingredient is not active
if it's active sometimes and it's not
active sometimes then it's not active
positive
was there a way the difference
I found people get hot they go to sleep
so in inside this there's nothing that
can tickle in your head
yeah
get used to it okay if
you answer today in any investment the
inside the investment there is not
anything which can make you move don't
uh tourism is to smoke
there's nothing you can say to your
boyfriend that will make him stay all
the time
if there is such a thing that everybody
would say then nobody would lose their
boyfriend
go away
if one investment has inside of it the
ability to make money then everybody
would do that and everybody would make
money but it's not true
foreign
I only work
three days a week
foreign
I counted the other day how many
projects and companies I have
it's 200.
and I'm I'm not nervous or I'm not like
oh you know
they're all nice they're all working
nice and I'm not like crazy
I don't work so hard
someone told me this has the recipe book
for the best coffee and I want the
recipe for okay
foreign
seriously we don't care
this way and he thinks we are crazy
it's not crazy I have time to go drive
for one hour to get a coffee
I want you to be like that
just
relaxed so people say
be relaxed don't have money I say no no
live relax and have money
and
your marriage should never get boring or
old
ER
if you understand the cause
if you understand how something works
your whole life is happy enough
okay so how does it says
we talked about it last night I'm going
to give you a new idea
different idea
it's not here this is wrong
selective language
the active ingredient in the aspirin is
not it's not some chemical
s
this is obvious
because it doesn't work
okay so your whole life you are making a
mistake she said to her you are paying
money for this
issues and sometimes it doesn't matter
you won't pay money for a car if it
doesn't work right
if you buy new Mercedes-Benz and the guy
says sometimes it goes sometimes it's a
question
is
if you pay for that you're crazy
so when it works why does it works
if we can learn why does it work when it
works then we can make it work all the
time
if you understand where your boyfriend
really came from you can keep him
and if you understand why he's nice
you can make him nice all the time
come on
there's three problems with the
boyfriend I'm just talking to Paula okay
yeah
first problem is to find them
yeah it should be a cause to find one
okay
some lady came to me she said
I want to find a boyfriend
then I she said I have a question for
you you're a monk
I heard that Tibetan Monks can tell the
future
we have a dice
and uh no we haven't made we can we go
like this which will die yes
you will meet your boyfriend here
she said I have a question I will meet
the boyfriend in the I'm thinking maybe
to go to a nightclub maybe I can meet
him there or maybe I will look on the
internet
if I find a boy in the nightclub
he will be the kind of boy who goes
tonight
foreign
if it's then
the boy who goes to the nightclub is a
little bit harder to keep
so much
I said what's your second choice
she said I am seeking internet maybe I
look in the internet
but she said that there's problem in
Internet
I said what's the problem
the boy you find in the internet he
loves his laptop more than you
know
you want to talk to him
he said where can I you do more tell me
where I will meet you
um
we have diced special dice it's made
from sheep
if you make strange sound do people
believe you
foreign
oh he's in the internet
I can see him
I see where you have to go
she said where do I have to go
I said you go to the old folks home
where they keep the old people actually
you go there
her head goes like this
then she said
you don't understand
I said what I don't understand
I want a young girl
you know I said no no you don't
understand
you think the internet makes the point
alternative
oh you think the nightclub will bring
the boys
and she said I
I have a good job
I have a good apartment
I come home from my job
I have to cook it I cook for like 45
minutes
it
each month five minutes
then wash everything for half hour not
knowing for 12 minutes
over one hour I'm cooking and cleaning
to eat for five minutes
I want to tell somebody about my job or
my problems
I said you want companionship
she said yeah that's what I wanted
if you want companionship you must give
companionship to somebody now
that's the only way to get companies
how does it work
if you go if if you want to find a
boyfriend
and if you go to the old folk Club
and you you visit somebody
can come be their companion
I talk to them you don't have to stay
very long just to have fun
you don't have to go every day go once a
week every two weeks
man because they want to companionship
when you go to their house
you give them companionship
when you are talking to them
who is watching
who is watching you I'm here
your mind is
your mind is always watching me
when the Mind watches you talking to the
old lady to make her happy
birthday
that puts a seed inside your mouth
then after uh two weeks
man you go and you sit in the coffee
shop the name says you sit down
you look up
door open soon
I'll tell you a true story
so that lady said who asked me
uh internet or nightclub
donut
so uh she went to the University of
Texas University
and she went to teach a class in Los
Angeles
it's already helping the old women for
six months
she planted many seeds
then she started to teach the yoga class
and she's always looking for the she's
waiting yeah
she's getting a little bit upset with me
she said he didn't come yeah
they close the door he found that box
she started
like Andre I'm sorry
I love my first time yeah
I got him
in that moment
the seed in her mind
from helping the woman
in her mind
and she saw someone who can give her
companionship yeah
foreign
when you plant apple seeds
and the apple tree growth
is
what happened to the Sea
where is the city
the growing of the tree kills the city
the power of the seed goes into the tree
the city
and that power will finish
every tree which grows will fall down
in Buddhism they still have a question
what made the tree father
you know the answer
when the tree grew that that's the cause
of the death of the tree
any songs
what kills a person okay
the the being born is what kills people
if the cause of Milling your husband is
you were helping the Old Navy and if you
stop helping the old lady then that
relationship must die
everything which has a cause Will Die 2
the reason you met a boy in a yoga class
is that you were helping the old woman
it put a seat in your mind
when you saw the question is
in most relationship you must start
fighting
you start to disagree
um
don't think you're a bad person the
possible
it's not your fault it's nature it's
natural issues what starts it has to
finish Society so I told her all this
no that's a bad news
I said no no you just plant some new
things
you keep planting seeds
right
so how do you make money
all the money in the world came for
giving and no other place
there's not one Euro in the world
economy that didn't come from giving
how do you get a boyfriend yeah
if you want yoga yoga to make you strong
and Young
what should you do go through two hours
because yoga also doesn't work
investment doesn't work
Aspen doesn't work
okay got it
talking to your husband when your
relationships start to get problem it
doesn't matter
it doesn't work all the time
okay if the airplane falls down
sometimes it's not good
foreign
thank you
okay
by the way obviously you can plant seeds
and it will come back from this through
this
is
if you have trouble with your husband
complaining
don't waste your time
don't talk to him
okay it's not his fault
you can talk maybe it will work maybe
it's not that means it doesn't work
foreign
because it grows Everything grows
on the Inside the Mind it goes like the
tree The Man shows
the power doubles every day
my company is the fastest growing
Manufacturing Company in the history of
us
New York
okay so we're going to take a break
before
now we're going to go to his book
his book is about the Angel and the
devil
today we should have three questions
Angel says no no one is enough
you have a devil and angel in your own
mind right all the time
your mind is always disgusting
in this system
you want to start a fight
you want to watch your mind
the mind has inside of the Angel and the
demo
the angel sorry the girl says you want
to find a boy
then you say yes
then he says I think you need the lawyer
yeah
okay don't apply the people
the red
it was really works
be careful somebody says really work you
said no no no no no no no
devil is talking
about you buy the red
Stone it really works when you hear
really works then don't believe the
person yes
he says buy the red or maybe pink you
think about that
the angel says forget the lipstick
don't think about red or pink
just go to the old person's home
somebody
give them companionship
basketball
close your eyes
pick up anyone
it will really work
okay
sit in your house he will come
so I I played a lot of States I I want
to be happy
to have a beautiful relationship I I
have all the women I keep her secretly
machine
20 years
and then my relationship is so beautiful
so
you can do okay crazy you know the devil
says
he says red lipstick or pink lipstick or
he says internet or he says nightclub
the angel says help lonely person
Ally really
impress answer the devil says do good
marketing do good advertising do good
product development do good accounting
do good hiring today
um
the angel says help the poor people
I told the story your last name I don't
know yeah
I went to yoga class in New York
I plan to stay for money
then I want to say maybe it will come
back without working
so I went to the yoga class
one guy came up to me yeah
he put a hundred thousand dollars in my
bag
I never met him in my life
okay
it's the real it's the real scene
it's a real active ingredient
just help other people
that's all you have to do
now in your mind
argument is starting
I like the argument
I want the argument
I want in your mind there is some doubt
about me
foreign
looks a little strange sounds very
strange
so maybe maybe he knows something
the angel and girl start to talk
you will go tomorrow like Monday you
will go to your job
somebody will come into your office
this investment really works yes
helping other people
now there's some technique you have to
know
I just told you that if you want Apple
you have to apply the apathy
but you need more information
you know many people who give money to
other people they didn't get rich they
got broke
person yeah
also you know very cheap people who are
very rich
we need more information
there is some farming technique
we'll talk about that after the prayer
if you hear that technique
just
just use it
and what you want you can get it
after you have money
foreign
if you have any special problems
if you have a special question specific
if you want to fix something about your
husband but you don't want to talk about
in front of the other people
just come and ask me doing this right
okay
try to make it short because other
people also have a problem
you didn't have time to talk to me
so in this system
we want you to become schizophrenic
did you did you have these kids
he said yes but it started
you watch your own mind
you learn to watch your own mind
I asked the angel to come in your mind
the angel is always saying the same
thing
Angel just says one thing
launch the inceptions
the Devil
he's he's giving you choices
go to nightclub go to what's the
internet what did you want on it don't
believe the government
he's going to always give you choices
in the diamond business there's a trick
when you sell the diamond they teach you
there's a trick
in the store diamond store
you always keep two diamonds
one is yellow
I never did this okay I heard it
system they say I I meet them
the guy is buying diamond for his uh his
fiance
then they come together
then you you take out the yellow diamond
this diamond is very clean
no spots completely
then the guy he thinks is good usually
the guy he doesn't see anything I know
they got so much
oh don't worry I have another time
being the the guy says yeah that's good
the girls
black spot
or cash
you give three bad choices very fast
credit card or cash
blue box or a red box
they forgot to both diamonds love you
it's called the two bad choices trick is
so the devil is always giving you
hello
maybe you should use red lipstick maybe
you should use pink
it is
maybe you should go to the Internet
maybe you should go to nightclub
foreign maybe you should ask your
husband not to criticize you maybe you
should stay quiet
all of his choices
your husband criticize you
don't think I should talk to him or I
shouldn't talk to him
don't criticize other people
should I make my art studio in the third
this around this mall or should I make
in the future
don't worry about it
help another person who wants to start
Art Studio
thank you
artistic
probably I think then it's two Studios
will come to you for free I don't
pretend for it again
you see all that trouble all the
suffering all the exhaustion is not
necessary foreign
foreign
just think if seed doesn't give the same
thing there's a big problem
what did you plan this year
but I don't know what's going to come on
just think do you have to think it's
good luck
you take the seed from the birthday
it will always make plastic never mingle
it's good luck
try to understand it's difficult okay
I'm I'm the angel I'm talking I'm
talking but I'm very rude
the devil says don't have too many
people you will be tired
you can't plant a watermelon seed and
get a mango
is
tired is bad
no energy
when you help us
helping can only give you more energy
it's not possible to get tired from
happening
if you plant a watermelon in your garden
after one month
and you see mango
what happened
It's Magic
not really are you talking in your real
life if if it happens
in your beautiful Paris Garden you have
the most beautiful flowers in the world
I'm very jealous
did you plant watermelon when something
else comes out mango what do you think
I think you can think maybe there was a
mango seed there before I planted the
watermelons
if you get tired
after you help someone I probably get
it's not coming from
coming from not helping someone before
that is
feeling tired is a memo
helping someone is uh
um
try to some guy asked me in America
everybody wants a green card
you know Green Card
all right it's an immigration crime
permanent immigration
you know the guy came to me
I'm illegal immigrants
I have an idea
I'm going to pay American Girl to
married
then next year I divorce yeah okay
I said
this is the green card
this is the LIE
this is helping someone else to find a
place to believe
okay
then between there's mango yeah okay you
helped someone else to find a place to
live
if you go to the immigration and if they
believe you it's not because you lied is
the LIE came before the green card no
yeah
but it was not the cause of
it
is
because this is a bad thing
this is a good thing
this one
actually here it just came before
a lie cannot produce a good thing
okay life doesn't work
now you tell me why
airplane that's good
yeah life doesn't work
it doesn't work all the time okay
sometimes
sometimes you lie the person believes
you
what is the LIE massage
the lies band
okay really the LIE is not a member okay
I hate eggplant
it feels sticky okay
yeah people will lie to you
see it didn't cause the glucose
it came before the green card but it
didn't cause the green
cards
some people go to yoga
they look great yoga
this is the yoga
this is looking great this is
helping sick people
what's the cause of her looking great
okay
helping people
yoga came between but it's just the
accident
you have to understand the real causes
then you can make money yeah you have a
beautiful Partners
um so the devil alone he will always
tell you
don't take Vitamin C take access
he wants you to think about
yellow diamond and black okay
both choices
this was
Berry doesn't make you healthy
the vitamin C doesn't make you happy
so people take vitamin they get cancer
some people smoke all the time they
lived in 95.
okay you know that
um so don't listen to him
what you want
to
connect what you don't want to go
stop doing to other people
I went to China
I spent about three months two three
months a year in China
why do I go to China
they've killed one million Tibetan
people
at my teacher's family don't the family
my Monastery was burnt
all the books
ten thousand miles
but I go to China
so you
say
you you go to the difficult place
and you can make better seats
if you want to be strong
and help the very sick people
if you want the most beautiful girl
I'm the most ugly old person
um
go to the difficult place
and and listen to your mind
because the mind will will argue
the demon will give you bad bad idea
okay
I'll give you some more of the poem
that demon made a very smart things
he said you don't want to get rid of me
I have to stay in um
you know the angel tell you to take care
of other people
I tell you to take care of yourself
if you kick me out
of your mind
if the angel is here all the time
you'll get tired
even don't go to your old person's home
go to night club it's not fun to go to
your old person
you want a boyfriend for fun you have to
go to a nightclubs
take care of yourself
don't take care of other people
if you kick out the devil
you're going to have a problem
no you don't understand
you told this guy his whole life take
care of yourself
sometimes he has money sometimes he
doesn't have money
sometimes he's sick sometimes he's
healthy
sometimes his girlfriend say I love you
sometimes he says
this is what you did to him
to think about other people is the
smartest way to think about yourself
to take care of yourself is the best way
to take care of other people
um
we don't need you
we don't need to take care of me
when you take care of other persons
no no when I take care of other people
that takes care of me and I'm not sure
okay okay
what does the devil says
foreign
you take it sometimes it works sometimes
it doesn't work it's not active
this is
in a devil said you cannot you cannot
get me out of your mind
he said karma put me here
Buddha cannot change cover professions
he said you planted seed for me
Karma put me in your mind
foreign
don't go to help the old person tonight
go to the old person at six o'clock then
go to the nightclub
s
if you don't go to the old person and
you go to the nightclub you won't meet
anybody
if you do have some money
yeah
it's the same for business
he wants you to go to the nightclub
without helping the operator
how do you get rid of
it
there's a seat in your mind
how do you
understand more
what's the seed for understanding
money
it's very interesting
if you want the angel to win in your
mind
share share what you understand
it will make the Angels stronger
teach other people
teach the people you know
you know many people
they are struggling to make money
they have relationship problems
and what problem they have today they
will have in five years and they will
have the same problem in 10 years and
they will have the same time it's not
going to change
that I didn't find the right boy
they think I didn't find the right job
she
needs or I need a different yoga teacher
I'm too fat
they're thinking wrong you see
they don't know
just help them foreign
you you know you know you have many
friends you have family
they are having a hard time
and it won't get better
what color they have now will get worse
this is the human life
the seed which create the life is
getting old
everybody getting older
economy is very difficult
the whole relationships we can't be
happy with our relationship but if we
have relationship we have a problem
but the
Vietnamese
everybody
you know has the same problems
it's not going to change if they find a
new job or a new boyfriend
they are not fixing the cause
so now you have some
foreign
and for the rest of your life
your husband was complaining about you
you will get angry
you will prepare something to say to you
my husband call you stupid
mind you you do a small quick meditation
I know what I'm going to tell him
then you you start to talk then you hear
me what
Angel is talking
later later
I don't know
why has your husband criticizing you
tonight
what did the guy say on June 25th at 9
20.
he said if my husband criticize me I
should stop criticizing other people
oh really I don't know
what you're going to say
hello
I'm going to tell him he's stupid
if you call him stupid he isn't Bloody
Muslims
then you have to see stupid husband next
week awesome
maybe better to be quiet
so I curse you
you're going to get angry at your
husband
my best students
they look the most confused
you can teach in the
coffee shop
you can teach in your house at the
kitchen tables
please teach okay
I'm asking you please teach shoes
because this way the angel will get
strong in your mind
and you will help all those other people
you can't understand what it feels like
to have all the money you want and you
see other people who cannot who are
working so hard for money and they are
doing the wrong thing
but you have beautiful beautiful
relationship because you understand
things foreign
all of them going to die
please help other people
good night did you have a question yeah
that's nice
how do you
plant the seeds to make the difference
to get the difference between an Android
in the first place
okay
by the way if you have a question
afterwards they can help you this new
Mercedes
NFL is teaching in Paris a lot and he's
going to teach more and Rihanna is
teaching his point so cecia and Carl
they know a lot they can help you okay
just ask them questions
he charges cost one person
she charges one coffee
that sounds good
also online there are 7 000 hours of
video and audio
songs 20
000 pages of translation
and there's 15 years of courses
um how do you know when the devil is
talking I mean the angel is talking
about
the angel will always win
the angel will always talk about helping
other people
the Angels always say the same thing
nervous system
so that's very easy way to tell who's
talking
Yeah
by itself
it's a very good question
nothing is Itself by itself
to the devil the angel looks like them
in your life
the angel is not the angels
I gave a talk in a city in China called
Guangzhou see the name
and one one lady came she raised her
head the infamous summer
I didn't come here to learn how to give
money I came here to learn how to make
money
if I listen to you I'm going to lose all
my money
so yeah everything can appear a
different way if the person has seen in
them
but you can change everything
nothing is unchangeable
foreign
with your husband or your wife for 20
years you can change it
if you didn't have fun with your partner
for 10 years
if your whole life you're struggling for
money
in the world you can stop War
s
this system is very powerful
it's a system with trapezium okay any
other questions
taking care of yourself is the most
beautiful thing
the most difficult thing in human life
is to be happy
it's much more easy to make money
it's much more easy to make a million
dollars than to be happy
and it's the most beautiful thing
if you can make yourself happy you have
succeeded
you make other people happy and that
makes you happy
you make yourself happy I think it's
better
foreign
a
consequences
but the goal is to make both happy
the devil wants you to make a choice
yeah you can be happy
yellow diamond or BlackBerry
um
some people told me I know poor people
who are happy
yeah
I said I also know poor people who are
unhappy
then they said I know rich people who
are unhappy yeah
I think better to be rich and happy
okay it's all right it's not a problem
you cannot make other people happy if
you are not happy
so it's a great goodness
yeah
and you cannot be successful or wealthy
or you cannot have a good relationship
without giving those things to other
people
the nature of the universe is that in
order for one person to be happy we all
have to be
here
any other questions
okay I have to go to a birthday party
foreign
people ask me a question they said do
you know Dalai Lama it is
then I said oh we are we are like this
they said alone
some other people were there
how many people 600.
hello
in Washington
then uh
I'm
34 tables away from you
with binocular I can't see him yeah
nobody wants to eat everybody wants to
watch him that's not very emotions
everybody wants to know uh
and they brought the big plate of fruit
is
very holy
night
probably he will collect it
they brought the food
foreign
you have a lot of fun
and you're always enjoying your life
that's why he's always smiling
it's so fun to have other people
so don't think your spiritual person
um
foreign
so I was saying somebody very special
here is in this place it's not important
you don't know that person
um but this person is responsible but
older sister of this person is
responsible for us to be here together
tonight for anatone and Adriana to come
since a few years and this person is
Syria
you know and so I wanted to be transmit
to all our love and blessings
to us here through Uganda which is
I would like to thank you
oh Carlton they've bought them
uh we have we have a schedule you can
see we have a restaurant
there's coffee there yes
we are booked for three years
every day
almost every hour already
I said everywhere in the world people
invite me I I just go people ask me to
come then I go
except Paris
yes I invite myself
difficult
most difficult place
so we ask you to come back yeah I'm
asking you to ask me okay
so the academic content people out okay
but make sure we have the email okay
right
you introduced to see
is
it
um
their arms thank you
good night